Start the play
And I can serve you better
Start to chill
Emotions scale
So I'm no longer forced
To keep my vital functions
Synthesize me
And drape those
I need to start again
I need to make a difference
All unguarded
All without
The will to play along
The numbers in child's fingers
I'm home
I'm here in Malta and today I was in St. Paul's and recorded a swimwear video with one bikini
and three bathing suits but then the sun went down so I couldn't film an intro.
why I'm here at my hotel recording this intro after I had dinner because I was
hungry so I hope you enjoy this video with a lot of sun more sun than now
My settings work
No stunted interactions
No doubts, no paranoia
I'm half
Alive
My skills
Attacked
I am always hearing her
I'm half alive
My skin's intact
I am always staring at the blade
The blade
My skin's intact
I am only staring at